<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>TeXariti</title>
    <link>http://texariti.com/</link>
    <description>Recent content on TeXariti</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <copyright>2015 Kendal King. All rights reserved.</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 09 Mar 2015 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="http://texariti.com/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    <item>
      <title>We are &#39;Go&#39; for launch!</title>
      <link>http://texariti.com/blog/launch-day/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 09 Mar 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://texariti.com/blog/launch-day/</guid>
      <description>

&lt;p class=&#34;drop-cap&#34;&gt;This is the home of &lt;i&gt;TeXariti&lt;/i&gt;, a group of web designers and programmers in Oklahoma City, Oklahoma. &lt;i&gt;TeXariti&lt;/i&gt; is a different kind of company. Our designers and team members are all friends. We also share a common commitment to others.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&#34;putting-people-first:634b40171687cf310cd64bbdaed43ea2&#34;&gt;Putting people first&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;You might wonder where the name &amp;ldquo;&lt;em&gt;TeXariti&lt;/em&gt;&amp;rdquo; came from. It comes from two ancient Greek words and means a gift that was not earned. We know that we aren&amp;rsquo;t who we are because of us. We didn&amp;rsquo;t get here on our own, and we want to remember that. We want our new company to be for others. This business isn&amp;rsquo;t just about money. It is about helping people. To put people first.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&#34;a-community-of-teaching-and-learning:634b40171687cf310cd64bbdaed43ea2&#34;&gt;A community of teaching and learning&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We are building not only a business but a community of learners and teachers. Every member on our team has different gifts. We are going to be teaching and learning from each other&amp;hellip; and opening up our meetings to the wider Oklahoma City community. Anyone who wants to learn about design, programming or wants to know how to start a business can come, free of charge!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you are interested in joining us in one of our classes, keep checking back on our homepage. We will let you know when we know a place and time we will be meeting. Once we get the bugs worked out we will be putting our classes on Youtube so everyone can benefit.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&#34;our-new-website:634b40171687cf310cd64bbdaed43ea2&#34;&gt;Our new website&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Thank you for dropping by our new website. We think you will like what you see!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Our &lt;a href=&#34;http://texariti.com/roadmap/&#34;&gt;Roadmap&lt;/a&gt; page will let you know how we work on web projects. We are methodical and professional; we want to get it right! We focus on communication between our clients and the designers. We try to understand you, who you are, what your company stands for, and then bring that out on the screen.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Take a look at the bulletin board on our &lt;a href=&#34;http://texariti.com/team/&#34;&gt;Team Page&lt;/a&gt;. As our team grows we are going to tack up a slip of paper for each member. :-)  Designing that page was a LOT of fun!!!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Our &lt;a href=&#34;http://texariti.com/projects/&#34;&gt;Projects&lt;/a&gt; page right is waiting for our first screenshots, but you can see the layout. We chose an elegant gray look for the page so that the rich colors of the screenshots will stand out. We make a point to put the &lt;em&gt;content&lt;/em&gt; of the page first. The design should always support and lift up the content.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Finally, take a look at our &lt;a href=&#34;http://texariti.com/contact/&#34;&gt;Contact&lt;/a&gt; page. It was snowing the day that page was designed, and a cold, snowy scene seemed appropriate! :-)&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&#34;great-things-are-coming:634b40171687cf310cd64bbdaed43ea2&#34;&gt;Great things are coming!&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We have a lot of plans for this website over the next few months. We are going to let you know how to have the best website you can possibly have. You will find practical advice on social media, marketing, and Google so be sure to bookmark us in your browser.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Thank you for dropping by! We hope to hear from you soon!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Yours,&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Kendal King&lt;br&gt;
&lt;em&gt;designer&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Roadmap</title>
      <link>http://texariti.com/roadmap/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://texariti.com/roadmap/</guid>
      <description>&lt;div class=&#34;container-fluid&#34;&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;row roadmap-viewport&#34;&gt;
    &lt;div class=&#34;col-sm-18 col-sm-offset-3&#34;&gt;
      &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;
      &lt;h1 class=&#34;tx-center&#34;&gt;The road to a &lt;nobr&gt;website&lt;/nobr&gt; you love!&lt;/h1&gt;
    &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;


&lt;div class=&#34;container&#34;&gt;

  &lt;div class=&#34;row roadmap-section&#34;&gt;
    &lt;div class=&#34;col-sm-18 col-sm-offset-3&#34;&gt;
      &lt;div class=&#34;roadmap-step&#34;&gt;
        &lt;p class=&#34;drop-cap&#34;&gt;Designing a website is a partnership between the client and the designer.&lt;/p&gt;
        &lt;p&gt;Communication is essential. &lt;i&gt;TeXariti&lt;/i&gt; needs to know what goals you have for your organization. What message you want your website to send? What do you want to convey to your customer or prospect?&lt;/p&gt;
        &lt;p&gt;To help build communication, we will follow a few well-defined steps.&lt;/p&gt;
        &lt;p&gt;The best way to build something unique is to do it in stages. Designers call it &amp;ldquo;Agile development.&amp;rdquo;&lt;/p&gt;
        &lt;ul&gt;
          &lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Step 1.&lt;/strong&gt; Lets say you want a static, great-looking landing page first. We would do that.&lt;/li&gt;
          &lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Step 2.&lt;/strong&gt; Then you want blog-posting ability on a Word Press engine. We would do that.&lt;/li&gt;
          &lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Step 3.&lt;/strong&gt; Next you want a newsletter designed and formatted. We would do that.&lt;/li&gt;
          &lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Step 4.&lt;/strong&gt; You want a mobile version of the newsletter. We would do that.&lt;/li&gt;
          &lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Step 5.&lt;/strong&gt; Next you want a Shopify store added into your website. We would do that.&lt;/li&gt;
        &lt;/ul&gt;
        &lt;p&gt;This lets the client make decisions as they go and adapt to what is working and what isn&#39;t just right. You always want the bulk of your effort going into two things that are already working. A lot of people start something, have it work a little, and then say &#34;Hey, we could do also do C and D and E.&#34; If A and B are working, first focus on making A and B work as best as possible. Only then do you think about C.&lt;/p&gt;
        &lt;p&gt;Defining steps also allow the client pay for the project in stages. You only pay for what &lt;i&gt;TeXariti&lt;/i&gt; is currently doing. There is no long-term lock-in. You own the website and all code behind it.&lt;/p&gt;
      &lt;/div&gt;
    &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;

  &lt;!-- ==================================== --&gt;

  &lt;div class=&#34;row roadmap-section&#34;&gt;
    &lt;div class=&#34;col-sm-14 col-sm-offset-5&#34;&gt;
      &lt;div class=&#34;roadmap-arrowbox-wrapper&#34;&gt;
        &lt;div class=&#34;arrowbox-1 hvr-grow-shadow&#34;&gt;
          &lt;div class=&#34;roadmap-question&#34;&gt;I&#39;m interested! I have a lot of questions. How do we begin?&lt;/div&gt;
        &lt;/div&gt;
      &lt;/div&gt;
    &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;

  &lt;div class=&#34;row roadmap-section&#34;&gt;
    &lt;div class=&#34;col-sm-18 col-sm-offset-3&#34;&gt;
      &lt;div class=&#34;roadmap-step&#34;&gt;
        &lt;h3&gt;1. First conversation&lt;/h3&gt;
        &lt;p&gt;In our first conversation you can share with us what kind of website you are thinking you need.&lt;/p&gt;
        &lt;p&gt;Once we get a feel for what you want your website to be, we can give you a general cost that you may be looking at.&lt;/p&gt;
      &lt;/div&gt;
    &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;

  &lt;!-- ==================================== --&gt;

  &lt;div class=&#34;row roadmap-section&#34;&gt;
    &lt;div class=&#34;col-sm-14 col-sm-offset-5&#34;&gt;
      &lt;div class=&#34;roadmap-arrowbox-wrapper&#34;&gt;
        &lt;div class=&#34;arrowbox-1 hvr-grow-shadow&#34;&gt;
          &lt;div class=&#34;roadmap-question&#34;&gt;I know I need a good website, but it all seems so confusing. How can I know what I need?&lt;/div&gt;
        &lt;/div&gt;
      &lt;/div&gt;
    &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;


  &lt;div class=&#34;row roadmap-section&#34;&gt;
    &lt;div class=&#34;col-sm-18 col-sm-offset-3&#34;&gt;
      &lt;div class=&#34;roadmap-step&#34;&gt;
        &lt;h3&gt;2. Informal chat&lt;/h3&gt;

        &lt;p&gt;We can meet in person, over the phone or by internet chat. If you are in the Oklahoma City area we can meet at your convenience. We will talk with you about your business or your church and what you are wanting from a web project.&lt;/p&gt;

        &lt;p&gt;We will talk about you, who you are.&lt;/p&gt;

        &lt;ul&gt;
          &lt;li&gt;What are your goals?&lt;/li&gt;
          &lt;li&gt;What is your business/church about?&lt;/li&gt;
          &lt;li&gt;Are you a business? What do you sell?&lt;/li&gt;
          &lt;li&gt;What do you want your web visitors to know about you?&lt;/li&gt;
          &lt;li&gt;What impression do you want your visitors to feel about you?&lt;/li&gt;
          &lt;li&gt;Who is your target customer or unreached group?&lt;/li&gt;
          &lt;li&gt;What are you doing to reach them now?&lt;/li&gt;
        &lt;/ul&gt;

        &lt;p&gt;&lt;i&gt;TeXariti&lt;/i&gt; will put together a plan for your website. By determining the requirements you have. &lt;i&gt;TeXariti&lt;/i&gt; will also have suggestions about how to make your online presence the most effective it can be.&lt;/p&gt;

        &lt;p&gt;One helpful thing we will ask is to think of what websites you think look good to you. Knowing what you like in other organization&#39;s websites will help us understand what you may be wanting for your site.&lt;/p&gt;

      &lt;/div&gt;
    &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;

  &lt;!-- ==================================== --&gt;

  &lt;div class=&#34;row roadmap-section&#34;&gt;
    &lt;div class=&#34;col-sm-14 col-sm-offset-5&#34;&gt;
      &lt;div class=&#34;roadmap-arrowbox-wrapper&#34;&gt;
        &lt;div class=&#34;arrowbox-1 hvr-grow-shadow&#34;&gt;
          &lt;div class=&#34;roadmap-question&#34;&gt;When do I find out how much this is going to cost?&lt;/div&gt;
        &lt;/div&gt;
      &lt;/div&gt;
    &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;


  &lt;div class=&#34;row roadmap-section&#34;&gt;
    &lt;div class=&#34;col-sm-18 col-sm-offset-3&#34;&gt;
      &lt;div class=&#34;roadmap-step&#34;&gt;
        &lt;h3&gt;3. Proposal and estimates&lt;/h3&gt;

        &lt;p&gt;A great website isn&#39;t a cost, it is an investment. Whether you are a for-profit business or a non-profit organization, a beautiful, effective web presence will bring in new customers and members.&lt;/p&gt;

        &lt;p&gt;After we have arrived at a list of project goals, &lt;i&gt;TeXariti&lt;/i&gt; will compose an estimate that includes clear milestones.&lt;/p&gt;

        &lt;p&gt;In this process, together we will decide on the scope of the project. We will have a list that specifies what &lt;i&gt;TeXariti&lt;/i&gt;, as the developer, will do for you. We will also have a list that specifies what you as a client will do (like what content or photos you may provide). We will also agree on what the project scope does not include. By setting expectations early we will be able to have a productive partnership.&lt;/p&gt;
      &lt;/div&gt;
    &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;

  &lt;!-- ==================================== --&gt;

  &lt;div class=&#34;row roadmap-section&#34;&gt;
    &lt;div class=&#34;col-sm-14 col-sm-offset-5&#34;&gt;
      &lt;div class=&#34;roadmap-arrowbox-wrapper&#34;&gt;
        &lt;div class=&#34;arrowbox-1 hvr-grow-shadow&#34;&gt;
          &lt;div class=&#34;roadmap-question&#34;&gt;Who is going to work on my project?&lt;/div&gt;
        &lt;/div&gt;
      &lt;/div&gt;
    &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;

  &lt;div class=&#34;row roadmap-section&#34;&gt;
    &lt;div class=&#34;col-sm-18 col-sm-offset-3&#34;&gt;
      &lt;div class=&#34;roadmap-step&#34;&gt;
        &lt;h3&gt;4. Meet the Team&lt;/h3&gt;

        &lt;p&gt;We will go over the plans together with the team that will work on your project. We want to be sure to clearly understand what you are needing and expecting from your website. We also will have many suggestions on how to expand your business or organization with an effective web presence.&lt;/p&gt;

        &lt;p&gt;We will also answer any questions you have. We want you to be pleased with every step in the process!&lt;/p&gt;
      &lt;/div&gt;
    &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;

  &lt;!-- ==================================== --&gt;

  &lt;div class=&#34;row roadmap-section&#34;&gt;
    &lt;div class=&#34;col-sm-14 col-sm-offset-5&#34;&gt;
      &lt;div class=&#34;roadmap-arrowbox-wrapper&#34;&gt;
        &lt;div class=&#34;arrowbox-1 hvr-grow-shadow&#34;&gt;
          &lt;div class=&#34;roadmap-question&#34;&gt;How is my website going to work?&lt;/div&gt;
        &lt;/div&gt;
      &lt;/div&gt;
    &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;

  &lt;div class=&#34;row roadmap-section&#34;&gt;
    &lt;div class=&#34;col-sm-18 col-sm-offset-3&#34;&gt;
      &lt;div class=&#34;roadmap-step&#34;&gt;
        &lt;h3&gt;5. Graybox Prototype!&lt;/h3&gt;

        &lt;p&gt;Many designers like to lay out a website using gray boxes and dummy text before they work on the actual design. It is the web-design equivalent of sketching a design on paper.&lt;/p&gt;

        &lt;p&gt;We will make a clickable, working website framework for you. It won&#39;t be pretty yet, but it will help you get a feel for how your website will work.&lt;/p&gt;

      &lt;/div&gt;
    &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;

  &lt;!-- ==================================== --&gt;

  &lt;div class=&#34;row roadmap-section&#34;&gt;
    &lt;div class=&#34;col-sm-14 col-sm-offset-5&#34;&gt;
      &lt;div class=&#34;roadmap-arrowbox-wrapper&#34;&gt;
        &lt;div class=&#34;arrowbox-1 hvr-grow-shadow&#34;&gt;
          &lt;div class=&#34;roadmap-question&#34;&gt;Sounds good. When do I make the decision to move forward?&lt;/div&gt;
        &lt;/div&gt;
      &lt;/div&gt;
    &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;

  &lt;div class=&#34;row roadmap-section&#34;&gt;
    &lt;div class=&#34;col-sm-18 col-sm-offset-3&#34;&gt;
      &lt;div class=&#34;roadmap-step&#34;&gt;
        &lt;h3&gt;6. Project Confirmation&lt;/h3&gt;
        &lt;p&gt;Once you are satisfied with the project plans and we agree on an estimate, we can get started. If the project scope requires it, we will exchange contracts and accept a deposit.&lt;/p&gt;
      &lt;/div&gt;
    &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;

  &lt;!-- ==================================== --&gt;

  &lt;div class=&#34;row roadmap-section&#34;&gt;
    &lt;div class=&#34;col-sm-14 col-sm-offset-5&#34;&gt;
      &lt;div class=&#34;roadmap-arrowbox-wrapper&#34;&gt;
        &lt;div class=&#34;arrowbox-1 hvr-grow-shadow&#34;&gt;
          &lt;div class=&#34;roadmap-question&#34;&gt;When do you need my content and photos? What if I have content, but I&#39;m not really happy with it? Can you help?&lt;/div&gt;
        &lt;/div&gt;
      &lt;/div&gt;
    &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;

  &lt;div class=&#34;row roadmap-section&#34;&gt;
    &lt;div class=&#34;col-sm-18 col-sm-offset-3&#34;&gt;
      &lt;div class=&#34;roadmap-step&#34;&gt;
        &lt;h3&gt;7. Content&lt;/h3&gt;

        &lt;h4&gt;Find your message and objectives&lt;/h4&gt;

        &lt;p&gt;We can help! The content of your website is the most important aspect to the success of your project. &lt;i&gt;TeXariti&lt;/i&gt; can help you compose the language for your website. &lt;i&gt;TeXariti&lt;/i&gt; will need your content in at least a rough draft form before &lt;i&gt;TeXariti&lt;/i&gt; can begin work on the design. We can work together to find just the right verbage for your site.&lt;/p&gt;

        &lt;!-- client provides the logo/identity and photography --&gt;

        &lt;h4&gt;Photos&lt;/h4&gt;

        &lt;p&gt;Photos will make or break a website! Most websites have photos that are far too small. The photos don&#39;t have to be perfect. Emotional impact is not based on photo quality, it comes from what is in the photo.&lt;/p&gt;

        &lt;p&gt;At this stage it will be time for you to supply photos, if applicable. The more photos to choose from the better. We can improve imperfect photos.&lt;/p&gt;
      &lt;/div&gt;
    &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;

  &lt;!-- ==================================== --&gt;

  &lt;div class=&#34;row roadmap-section&#34;&gt;
    &lt;div class=&#34;col-sm-14 col-sm-offset-5&#34;&gt;
      &lt;div class=&#34;roadmap-arrowbox-wrapper&#34;&gt;
        &lt;div class=&#34;arrowbox-1 hvr-grow-shadow&#34;&gt;
          &lt;div class=&#34;roadmap-question&#34;&gt;How long will my project take to finish?&lt;/div&gt;
        &lt;/div&gt;
      &lt;/div&gt;
    &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;

  &lt;div class=&#34;row roadmap-section&#34;&gt;
    &lt;div class=&#34;col-sm-18 col-sm-offset-3&#34;&gt;
      &lt;div class=&#34;roadmap-step&#34;&gt;
        &lt;h3&gt;8. We Design Your Website!&lt;/h3&gt;
        &lt;p&gt;The length of time it takes to finish your web project depends on how much content you have and how detailed the design is going to be. It also depends on the time it takes our clients to respond to our communications. Building an excellent website is a partnership... it takes a lot of talking!&lt;/p&gt;
        &lt;p&gt;Some projects can be completed in just a couple of weeks; large projects may take a few months. The good news is that large projects can be done in stages, so it doesn&#39;t take months to have something beautiful online.&lt;/p&gt;
      &lt;/div&gt;
    &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;

  &lt;!-- ==================================== --&gt;

  &lt;div class=&#34;row roadmap-section&#34;&gt;
    &lt;div class=&#34;col-sm-14 col-sm-offset-5&#34;&gt;
      &lt;div class=&#34;roadmap-arrowbox-wrapper&#34;&gt;
        &lt;div class=&#34;arrowbox-1 hvr-grow-shadow&#34;&gt;
          &lt;div class=&#34;roadmap-question&#34;&gt;When do I get to see my website?&lt;/div&gt;
        &lt;/div&gt;
      &lt;/div&gt;
    &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;

  &lt;div class=&#34;row roadmap-section&#34;&gt;
    &lt;div class=&#34;col-sm-18 col-sm-offset-3&#34;&gt;
      &lt;div class=&#34;roadmap-step&#34;&gt;
        &lt;h3&gt;9. Testing and Review&lt;/h3&gt;
        &lt;p&gt;When an author writes a book the first draft is never the final version! It takes time to refine, to shape, to phrase and re-phrase. Crafting a quality website can&#39;t be rushed. We will work with you, going over every detail, so that your website is the best that it can be!&lt;/p&gt;
      &lt;/div&gt;
    &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;

  &lt;!-- ==================================== --&gt;

  &lt;div class=&#34;row roadmap-section&#34;&gt;
    &lt;div class=&#34;col-sm-14 col-sm-offset-5&#34;&gt;
      &lt;div class=&#34;roadmap-arrowbox-wrapper&#34;&gt;
        &lt;div class=&#34;arrowbox-1 hvr-grow-shadow&#34;&gt;
          &lt;div class=&#34;roadmap-question&#34;&gt;I can&#39;t wait! I&#39;m excited!&lt;/div&gt;
        &lt;/div&gt;
      &lt;/div&gt;
    &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;

  &lt;div class=&#34;row roadmap-section&#34;&gt;
    &lt;div class=&#34;col-sm-18 col-sm-offset-3&#34;&gt;
      &lt;div class=&#34;roadmap-step&#34;&gt;
        &lt;h3&gt;10. Launch!&lt;/h3&gt;
        &lt;p&gt;Your new website is finished! Hours of work and careful attention to detail have come to an end, and the project is ready to go public. You will be able to study your completed website and let us know of any tiny details that need to be addressed. Once you are completely satisfied, we will upload your website to the host of your choice. Your website is viewable by the world!&lt;/p&gt;
      &lt;/div&gt;
    &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;

  &lt;!-- ==================================== --&gt;

  &lt;div class=&#34;row roadmap-section&#34;&gt;
    &lt;div class=&#34;col-sm-14 col-sm-offset-5&#34;&gt;
      &lt;div class=&#34;roadmap-arrowbox-wrapper&#34;&gt;
        &lt;div class=&#34;arrowbox-1 hvr-grow-shadow&#34;&gt;
          &lt;div class=&#34;roadmap-question&#34;&gt;What about after the launch? How will I know my website is as effective as it can be?&lt;/div&gt;
        &lt;/div&gt;
      &lt;/div&gt;
    &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;

  &lt;div class=&#34;row roadmap-section&#34;&gt;
    &lt;div class=&#34;col-sm-18 col-sm-offset-3&#34;&gt;
      &lt;div class=&#34;roadmap-step&#34;&gt;
        &lt;h3&gt;11. Performance Reviews&lt;/h3&gt;

        &lt;p&gt;We consider our clients to be our long-term partners, making sure that they have the best web experience possible. We won&#39;t leave you hanging!&lt;/p&gt;

        &lt;p&gt;If you want a great website, you don&#39;t just make a design and walk away and leave it sitting.&lt;/p&gt;

        &lt;!-- Monthly review of the site and addition of new features --&gt;
        &lt;ul&gt;
          &lt;li&gt;Is this design the best it can be in drawing visitors?&lt;/li&gt;
          &lt;li&gt;Is this design effective in converting visitors to customers?&lt;/li&gt;
          &lt;li&gt;How will success be measured?&lt;/li&gt;
          &lt;li&gt;What are the real-world results?&lt;/li&gt;
          &lt;li&gt;Are you, our client, still excited with your website? Are you proud to show it off to your friends?&lt;/li&gt;
          &lt;li&gt;What can we learn from your visitor statistics? Where are most of your visits coming from?&lt;/li&gt;
        &lt;/ul&gt;

        &lt;p&gt;Every so often we will conduct a performance review of your site. We want to make sure your website is the most effective tool it can be to promote your business or organization!&lt;/p&gt;
      &lt;/div&gt;
    &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;

  &lt;!-- ==================================== --&gt;

  &lt;div class=&#34;row roadmap-section&#34;&gt;
    &lt;div class=&#34;col-sm-14 col-sm-offset-5&#34;&gt;
      &lt;div class=&#34;roadmap-arrowbox-wrapper&#34;&gt;
        &lt;div class=&#34;arrowbox-1 hvr-grow-shadow&#34;&gt;
          &lt;div class=&#34;roadmap-question&#34;&gt;I&#39;m so happy! I love my new website, and everyone says how pretty it is!&lt;/div&gt;
        &lt;/div&gt;
      &lt;/div&gt;
    &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;

  &lt;div class=&#34;row roadmap-section&#34;&gt;
    &lt;div class=&#34;col-sm-18 col-sm-offset-3&#34;&gt;
      &lt;div class=&#34;roadmap-step&#34;&gt;
        &lt;p class=&#34;tx-center&#34;&gt;This is the part where you tell everyone you know about us.&lt;br&gt;:-)&lt;/p&gt;
      &lt;/div&gt;
    &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;

  &lt;!-- ==================================== --&gt;

&lt;/div&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Contact Us</title>
      <link>http://texariti.com/contact/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://texariti.com/contact/</guid>
      <description>&lt;div class=&#34;container&#34;&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;row&#34;&gt;
    &lt;div class=&#34;col-xs-24 col-sm-offset-13 col-sm-11&#34;&gt;

      &lt;br&gt;
      &lt;br&gt;
      &lt;br&gt;

      &lt;h2&gt;Contact Us!&lt;/h2&gt;

      &lt;br&gt;

      &lt;div class=&#34;contact-intro&#34;&gt;
        &lt;p&gt;Hello! Thank you for visiting our new website.&lt;/p&gt;

        &lt;p&gt;Just as there are seasons in the weather, there are seasons that companies go through. We have our Winters. Business can be tough! But Springtime will eventually come.&lt;/p&gt;

        &lt;p&gt;We at &lt;i&gt;TeXariti&lt;/i&gt; want to be there with you this Winter. We know the web. We can help you plan for your Spring. We can help you get the most out of your online presence. We can help you find fertile soil in which to plant.&lt;/p&gt;

        &lt;p&gt;We look forward to answering your questions. Send us an email, or give us a call. We hope to speak to you soon!&lt;/p&gt;

        &lt;p&gt;Have a great day!

        &lt;p&gt;And try to stay warm!&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;:-)&lt;/p&gt;

        &lt;p&gt;~ The Team at &lt;i&gt;TeXariti&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
      &lt;/div&gt;


      &lt;div class=&#34;contact-info&#34;&gt;
        &lt;div class=&#34;contact-name&#34;&gt;Kendal King&lt;/div&gt;
        &lt;div class=&#34;contact-eml&#34;&gt;
          &lt;br&gt;
          &lt;div class=&#34;eml3&#34;&gt;764ladnek&lt;/div&gt;
          &lt;div&gt;
            &lt;span class=&#34;eml1&#34;&gt;moc&lt;/span&gt;.
            &lt;span class=&#34;none&#34;&gt;_neddih-liame_&lt;/span&gt;
            &lt;span class=&#34;eml2&#34;&gt;liamg@&lt;/span&gt;
          &lt;/div&gt;
          &lt;br&gt;
         &lt;/div&gt;
        &lt;div class=&#34;contact-phone&#34;&gt;479-206-0283&lt;/div&gt;
      &lt;/div&gt;

      &lt;div class=&#34;contact-access&#34;&gt;
       &lt;p&gt;The email address above is coded in a way that automated spam programs won&#39;t find it. You will need to type it into your email program; it won&#39;t copy and paste.&lt;/p&gt;
       &lt;p&gt;For the visually disabled: Here is the email address in a sentence for screenreaders: Email &#34;&lt;i&gt;kendal&lt;/i&gt;&#34; and the number &#34;&lt;i&gt;467&lt;/i&gt;&#34; at the address &#34;&lt;i&gt;gmail&lt;/i&gt;&#34; that ends with &#34;&lt;i&gt;dot com&lt;/i&gt;.&#34;&lt;/p&gt;
      &lt;/div&gt;

    &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;

  &lt;div class=&#34;winter-girl&#34;&gt;
    &lt;div class=&#34;container-fluid&#34;&gt;
      &lt;div class=&#34;row&#34;&gt;
        &lt;div class=&#34;col-sm-8 col-sm-offset-2&#34;&gt;
         &lt;div class=&#34;thankyou&#34;&gt;Thank you!&lt;/div&gt;
        &lt;/div&gt;
      &lt;/div&gt;
    &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Projects</title>
      <link>http://texariti.com/projects/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://texariti.com/projects/</guid>
      <description>&lt;div class=&#34;project-viewport&#34;&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;container-fluid&#34;&gt;
    &lt;div class=&#34;row&#34;&gt;
      &lt;div class=&#34;col-sm-18 col-sm-offset-3&#34;&gt;
      &lt;/div&gt;
    &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;


&lt;div class=&#34;project-main&#34;&gt;

  &lt;div class=&#34;container-fluid&#34;&gt;
    &lt;div class=&#34;row&#34;&gt;
      &lt;div class=&#34;row&#34;&gt;

        &lt;div class=&#34;col-sm-18 col-sm-offset-3&#34;&gt;
          &lt;br&gt;
          &lt;h1 class=&#34;page-header (tx-center) (m4b)&#34;&gt;Projects&lt;/h1&gt;

          &lt;p class=&#34;lead&#34;&gt;We have exciting projects in progress! This is the future home of our portfolio.&lt;/p&gt;
        &lt;/div&gt;
    &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;

  &lt;!--
  These progress bars are better:  https://css-tricks.com/examples/ProgressBars/

  &lt;div class=&#34;project&#34;&gt;
    &lt;div class=&#34;container-fluid&#34;&gt;
      &lt;div class=&#34;row&#34;&gt;
        &lt;div class=&#34;col-sm-18 col-sm-offset-3&#34;&gt;

          &lt;h3&gt;Project Timeline&lt;/h3&gt;

          &lt;div class=&#34;timeline&#34;&gt;
            &lt;ul class=&#34;intervals clearfix&#34;&gt;
              &lt;li class=&#34;first&#34;&gt;March 1&lt;/li&gt;
              &lt;li&gt;March 8&lt;/li&gt;
              &lt;li&gt;March 15&lt;/li&gt;
              &lt;li&gt;March 22&lt;/li&gt;
              &lt;li&gt;March 29&lt;/li&gt;
              &lt;li&gt;April 5&lt;/li&gt;
              &lt;li class=&#34;last&#34;&gt;April 12&lt;/li&gt;
            &lt;/ul&gt;
            &lt;ul class=&#34;events&#34;&gt;
              &lt;li style=&#34;width: 40%; left: 5%;&#34;&gt;Erin Cook &lt;em&gt;(current)&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
              &lt;li style=&#34;width: 40.3%; left: 30%;&#34;&gt;Jeremy Sheets&lt;/li&gt;
              &lt;li style=&#34;width: 71.3%; left: 28.4%;&#34;&gt;Musician website &lt;em&gt;(under discussion)&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
            &lt;/ul&gt;
          &lt;/div&gt;

        &lt;/div&gt;
      &lt;/div&gt;
    &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
   --&gt;
  &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;


  &lt;div class=&#34;project&#34;&gt;
    &lt;div class=&#34;container-fluid&#34;&gt;
      &lt;div class=&#34;row&#34;&gt;
        &lt;div class=&#34;col-sm-18 col-sm-offset-3&#34;&gt;
          &lt;a href=&#34;#&#34;&gt;&lt;img class=&#34;project-photo img-responsive img-center&#34; src=&#34;http://placehold.it/950x600/333333/999999&amp;text=In+Progress!&#34; alt=&#34;&#34;&gt;&lt;/a&gt;
          &lt;h3&gt;Erin Elizabeth Cook&lt;/h3&gt;
          &lt;h4&gt;Gifted Actor and Acting Coach&lt;/h4&gt;
          &lt;p&gt;Erin is a gifted actress and an amazing teacher.  She has studied under some of the best teachers of the art of acting, and has appeared in Hollywood productions in TV and film. As a teacher, her care for her students is evident in how she strives to see them become the best they can be. Her career is one to watch!&lt;/p&gt;
          &lt;a class=&#34;btn btn-primary&#34; href=&#34;#&#34;&gt;View Project &lt;span class=&#34;glyphicon glyphicon-chevron-right&#34;&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/a&gt;
        &lt;/div&gt;
      &lt;/div&gt;
    &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;

    &lt;div class=&#34;blog-summary-divider&#34;&gt;
      &lt;div class=&#34;container-fluid&#34;&gt;
        &lt;div class=&#34;row&#34;&gt;
          &lt;div class=&#34;col-sm-8 col-sm-offset-8&#34;&gt;
            &lt;img src=&#34;../img/divider-2-by-kickthecork.com-181268.svg&#34; class=&#34;centered&#34; alt=&#34;divider&#34;&gt;
          &lt;/div&gt;
        &lt;/div&gt;
      &lt;/div&gt;
    &lt;/div&gt;


  &lt;div class=&#34;project&#34;&gt;
    &lt;div class=&#34;container-fluid&#34;&gt;
      &lt;div class=&#34;row&#34;&gt;
        &lt;div class=&#34;col-sm-18 col-sm-offset-3&#34;&gt;
          &lt;a href=&#34;#&#34;&gt;&lt;img class=&#34;project-photo img-responsive img-center&#34; src=&#34;http://placehold.it/950x600/333333/999999&amp;text=Planning+Steps&#34; alt=&#34;&#34;&gt;&lt;/a&gt;
          &lt;h3&gt;Jeremy Sheets&lt;/h3&gt;
          &lt;h4&gt;Cellist and Actor&lt;/h4&gt;
          &lt;p&gt;When Jeremy is on the strings of the cello, his hands may hold the instrument but the music comes from his heart. The atmosphere in the room changes when he begins to play. Jeremy is a performer, and is now expanding his performance skills as an actor on the stage and in film.&lt;/p&gt;
          &lt;a class=&#34;btn btn-primary&#34; href=&#34;#&#34;&gt;View Project &lt;span class=&#34;glyphicon glyphicon-chevron-right&#34;&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/a&gt;
        &lt;/div&gt;
      &lt;/div&gt;
    &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;

&lt;/div&gt; &lt;!-- .main --&gt;

&lt;div class=&#34;divider-2&#34;&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;container-fluid&#34;&gt;
    &lt;div class=&#34;row&#34;&gt;
      &lt;div class=&#34;col-sm-8 col-sm-offset-8&#34;&gt;
        &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;
        &lt;img src=&#34;../img/openclipart.org__johnny-automatic-fancy-flourish.svg&#34; class=&#34;centered&#34; alt=&#34;divider&#34;&gt;
      &lt;/div&gt;
    &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Team</title>
      <link>http://texariti.com/team/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://texariti.com/team/</guid>
      <description>&lt;!-- 2015-03-12__15:35:04 --&gt;

&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;

&lt;div class=&#34;team-main&#34;&gt;

  &lt;div class=&#34;container&#34;&gt;

    &lt;div class=&#34;row&#34;&gt;
      &lt;div class=&#34;col-sm-24 col-md-11&#34;&gt;

        &lt;div class=&#34;paper paper-shadow&#34;&gt;
          &lt;!-- Tack --&gt;
          &lt;div class=&#34;tx-center&#34;&gt;
            &lt;img class=&#34;centered&#34; style=&#34;width: 5rem;&#34; src=&#34;../img/openclipart.org-thumb-tack-2-plain.svg&#34; alt=&#34;divider&#34;&gt;
          &lt;/div&gt;

          &lt;div class=&#34;paper-textarea&#34;&gt;
            &lt;h2 class=&#34;&#34;&gt;About Us&lt;/h2&gt;
            &lt;p&gt;We are a team of web designers and programmers who are joining together to build state-of-the-art web projects.&lt;/p&gt;
          &lt;/div&gt;
        &lt;/div&gt;

        &lt;div class=&#34;postit postit-blue paper-shadow centered2 rotate-354&#34;&gt;
           &lt;!-- Tack --&gt;
            &lt;div class=&#34;tx-center&#34;&gt;
              &lt;img class=&#34;centered&#34; style=&#34;width: 5rem;&#34; src=&#34;../img/openclipart.org-thumb-tack-2-plain.svg&#34; alt=&#34;divider&#34;&gt;
            &lt;/div&gt;
            &lt;p class=&#34;tx-center&#34;&gt;&lt;i&gt;TeXariti&lt;/i&gt; sounds like the words &amp;lsquo;tech&amp;rsquo; and &amp;lsquo;care&amp;rsquo; with an &amp;lsquo;iti&amp;rsquo; on the end. Xariti sounds like &lt;nobr&gt;&amp;lsquo;charity&amp;rsquo;&lt;/nobr&gt; but with a &amp;lsquo;K&amp;rsquo;.&lt;/p&gt;
        &lt;/div&gt;

      &lt;/div&gt;

      &lt;div class=&#34;col-sm-24 col-md-offset-2 col-md-11&#34;&gt;
        &lt;div class=&#34;paper paper-shadow&#34;&gt;

          &lt;!-- Tack --&gt;
          &lt;div class=&#34;tx-center&#34;&gt;
            &lt;img class=&#34;centered&#34; style=&#34;width: 5rem;&#34; src=&#34;../img/openclipart.org-thumb-tack-2-plain.svg&#34; alt=&#34;divider&#34;&gt;
          &lt;/div&gt;

          &lt;div class=&#34;paper-textarea&#34;&gt;
            &lt;h3 class=&#34;&#34;&gt;What is &lt;span class=&#34;wide-spaced&#34;&gt;&amp;ldquo;TeXariti&amp;rdquo;?&lt;span&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
            &lt;p&gt;&lt;i&gt;TeXariti&lt;/i&gt; comes from two Greek words and means a gift that is not earned. Our name was chosen to remind us that we didn&#39;t get where we are alone. We want to use our gifts to help others.&lt;/p&gt;
            &lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
          &lt;/div&gt;

        &lt;/div&gt;
      &lt;/div&gt;
    &lt;/div&gt; &lt;!-- .row --&gt;


    &lt;div class=&#34;row&#34;&gt;
      &lt;div class=&#34;col-sm-24 col-md-11&#34;&gt;
        &lt;div class=&#34;paper paper-shadow&#34;&gt;

          &lt;!-- Tack --&gt;
          &lt;div class=&#34;tx-center&#34;&gt;
            &lt;img class=&#34;centered&#34; style=&#34;width: 5rem;&#34; src=&#34;../img/openclipart.org-thumb-tack-2-plain.svg&#34; alt=&#34;divider&#34;&gt;
          &lt;/div&gt;

          &lt;div class=&#34;paper-textarea&#34;&gt;
            &lt;img class=&#34;team-photo img-responsive img-center&#34; src=&#34;../photos/kendal_200x253.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;&#34;&gt;
            &lt;h3 class=&#34;tx-center&#34;&gt;Kendal&lt;/h3&gt;
            &lt;p class=&#34;tx-center&#34;&gt;&lt;em&gt;Designer, Business &lt;nobr&gt;Strategy&lt;/nobr&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
            &lt;p&gt;Kendal loves design and is a perfectionist when it comes to getting &amp;ldquo;just the right look.&amp;rdquo; He is studying the Lisp and Go programming languages.&lt;/p&gt;
            &lt;p&gt;Kendal has a B.A. in Bible from Oklahoma Baptist University. He is starting a church for people with disabilities and cancer patients, their families and caregivers.&lt;/p&gt;
            &lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Likes&lt;/em&gt;: Lisp, Emacs, Linux, design principles, Bible, Greek, church starting. Hopes to get into cooking and gardening.&lt;/p&gt;
            &lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Favorite meal&lt;/em&gt;: Steak and shrimp, fries with white gravy, breaded okra and hot buttered rolls.&lt;/p&gt;
            &lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Favorite dessert&lt;/em&gt;: Chocolate ice cream on a brownie!&amp;nbsp :-)&lt;/p&gt;
          &lt;/div&gt;

        &lt;/div&gt;
      &lt;/div&gt;

      &lt;div class=&#34;col-sm-24 col-md-offset-2 col-md-11&#34;&gt;

        &lt;div class=&#34;postit postit-yellow paper-shadow centered2&#34;&gt;
           &lt;!-- Tack --&gt;
            &lt;div class=&#34;tx-center&#34;&gt;
              &lt;img class=&#34;centered&#34; style=&#34;width: 5rem;&#34; src=&#34;../img/openclipart.org-thumb-tack-2-plain.svg&#34; alt=&#34;divider&#34;&gt;
            &lt;/div&gt;
            &lt;h3 class=&#34;tx-center&#34;&gt;More team members coming soon!&lt;br&gt;&lt;i&gt;...Excited!&lt;/i&gt;&lt;br&gt;:-)&lt;/h3&gt;
        &lt;/div&gt;

        &lt;!-- &lt;a href=&#34;../design/&#34;&gt; --&gt;
          &lt;div class=&#34;postit postit-purple paper-shadow centered2&#34;&gt;
             &lt;!-- Tack --&gt;
              &lt;div class=&#34;tx-center&#34;&gt;
                &lt;img class=&#34;centered&#34; style=&#34;width: 5rem;&#34; src=&#34;../img/openclipart.org-thumb-tack-2-plain.svg&#34; alt=&#34;divider&#34;&gt;
              &lt;/div&gt;
              &lt;h3 class=&#34;tx-center&#34;&gt;Lots of plans, too&lt;/h3&gt;
          &lt;/div&gt;
        &lt;!-- &lt;/a&gt; --&gt;

        &lt;div class=&#34;postit postit-pink paper-shadow centered2&#34;&gt;
           &lt;!-- Tack --&gt;
            &lt;div class=&#34;tx-center&#34;&gt;
              &lt;img class=&#34;centered&#34; style=&#34;width: 5rem;&#34; src=&#34;../img/openclipart.org-thumb-tack-2-plain.svg&#34; alt=&#34;divider&#34;&gt;
            &lt;/div&gt;
            &lt;h3 class=&#34;tx-center&#34;&gt;Writing on pink post-it notes is fun!&lt;br&gt;:-)&lt;/h3&gt;
        &lt;/div&gt;

      &lt;/div&gt;

    &lt;/div&gt; &lt;!-- .row --&gt;

  &lt;/div&gt; &lt;!-- .container --&gt;



  &lt;div class=&#34;container&#34;&gt;
    &lt;div class=&#34;row&#34;&gt;
      &lt;div class=&#34;col-sm-24 col-md-24&#34;&gt;

          &lt;div class=&#34;postit postit-white-crumbled-paper paper-shadow centered2&#34;&gt;
             &lt;!-- Tack --&gt;
              &lt;div class=&#34;tx-center&#34;&gt;
                &lt;img class=&#34;centered&#34; style=&#34;width: 5rem;&#34; src=&#34;../img/openclipart.org-thumb-tack-2-plain.svg&#34; alt=&#34;divider&#34;&gt;
              &lt;/div&gt;
              &lt;a href=&#34;../contact/&#34;&gt;
                &lt;h3 class=&#34;tx-center&#34;&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;red-marker&#34;&gt;Need help with your&lt;br&gt;website?&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;blue-marker&#34;&gt;Email us&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
              &lt;/a&gt;
          &lt;/div&gt;

    &lt;/div&gt; &lt;!-- .row --&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt; &lt;!-- .container --&gt;


&lt;/div&gt; &lt;!-- .main --&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>