<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Launch on TeXariti</title>
    <link>http://texariti.com/tags/launch/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Launch on TeXariti</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <copyright>2015 Kendal King. All rights reserved.</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 09 Mar 2015 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="http://texariti.com/tags/launch/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    <item>
      <title>We are &#39;Go&#39; for launch!</title>
      <link>http://texariti.com/blog/launch-day/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 09 Mar 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://texariti.com/blog/launch-day/</guid>
      <description>

&lt;p class=&#34;drop-cap&#34;&gt;This is the home of &lt;i&gt;TeXariti&lt;/i&gt;, a group of web designers and programmers in Oklahoma City, Oklahoma. &lt;i&gt;TeXariti&lt;/i&gt; is a different kind of company. Our designers and team members are all friends. We also share a common commitment to others.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&#34;putting-people-first:634b40171687cf310cd64bbdaed43ea2&#34;&gt;Putting people first&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;You might wonder where the name &amp;ldquo;&lt;em&gt;TeXariti&lt;/em&gt;&amp;rdquo; came from. It comes from two ancient Greek words and means a gift that was not earned. We know that we aren&amp;rsquo;t who we are because of us. We didn&amp;rsquo;t get here on our own, and we want to remember that. We want our new company to be for others. This business isn&amp;rsquo;t just about money. It is about helping people. To put people first.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&#34;a-community-of-teaching-and-learning:634b40171687cf310cd64bbdaed43ea2&#34;&gt;A community of teaching and learning&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We are building not only a business but a community of learners and teachers. Every member on our team has different gifts. We are going to be teaching and learning from each other&amp;hellip; and opening up our meetings to the wider Oklahoma City community. Anyone who wants to learn about design, programming or wants to know how to start a business can come, free of charge!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you are interested in joining us in one of our classes, keep checking back on our homepage. We will let you know when we know a place and time we will be meeting. Once we get the bugs worked out we will be putting our classes on Youtube so everyone can benefit.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&#34;our-new-website:634b40171687cf310cd64bbdaed43ea2&#34;&gt;Our new website&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Thank you for dropping by our new website. We think you will like what you see!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Our &lt;a href=&#34;http://texariti.com/roadmap/&#34;&gt;Roadmap&lt;/a&gt; page will let you know how we work on web projects. We are methodical and professional; we want to get it right! We focus on communication between our clients and the designers. We try to understand you, who you are, what your company stands for, and then bring that out on the screen.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Take a look at the bulletin board on our &lt;a href=&#34;http://texariti.com/team/&#34;&gt;Team Page&lt;/a&gt;. As our team grows we are going to tack up a slip of paper for each member. :-)  Designing that page was a LOT of fun!!!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Our &lt;a href=&#34;http://texariti.com/projects/&#34;&gt;Projects&lt;/a&gt; page right is waiting for our first screenshots, but you can see the layout. We chose an elegant gray look for the page so that the rich colors of the screenshots will stand out. We make a point to put the &lt;em&gt;content&lt;/em&gt; of the page first. The design should always support and lift up the content.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Finally, take a look at our &lt;a href=&#34;http://texariti.com/contact/&#34;&gt;Contact&lt;/a&gt; page. It was snowing the day that page was designed, and a cold, snowy scene seemed appropriate! :-)&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&#34;great-things-are-coming:634b40171687cf310cd64bbdaed43ea2&#34;&gt;Great things are coming!&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We have a lot of plans for this website over the next few months. We are going to let you know how to have the best website you can possibly have. You will find practical advice on social media, marketing, and Google so be sure to bookmark us in your browser.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Thank you for dropping by! We hope to hear from you soon!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Yours,&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Kendal King&lt;br&gt;
&lt;em&gt;designer&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>